Nitro Circus: The Movie is a action, comedy,
documentary film directed by Jeremy Rawle.
You will see Travis Pastrana and the whole Nitro Circus crew perform some of the most
ridiculous, awe-inspiring, and simply insane stunts ever caught on camera.
Coming to you in three dimensional glory, it will feel like
you are there sitting shotgun with the crew.
Self, played by Travis Pastrana.
Self, played by Jolene Van Vugt.
Self, played by Tommy Passemante.
Self, played by Jeremy Rawle.
Self, played by Gregg Godfrey.
Self, played by Greg Powell.
Nitro Circus: The Movie is a 2012 American 3D action comedy reality
film based on the MTV eponymous reality comedy series.
Directed by Gregg Godfrey and Jeremy Rawle, it was both a critical and commercial
failure, grossing little more than half its $7 million budget.
The film explores themes of stunt, motocross, mayhem.
The tone is lighthearted and uplifting.